https://www.ltg.de/en/privacy-statement/

Contact
Products & ServicesLTG Comfort Air TechnologyAir-Water SystemsLTG Induction UnitsLTG Fan Coil UnitsLTG Decentralised UnitsAccessoriesAir DiffusersLinear DiffusersSwirl and Ceiling Jet DiffusersAir diffusers for industry / large air flow ratesAir DistributionFlow Rate ControllersPressure ControllersShut-Off DampersInnovationInnovative Air FlowsEnergy-efficient TechniquesInnovative Product DesignServiceLTG Process Air TechnologyFansTangential FansCentrifugal FansAxial FansFahrtwind-SimulatorsFiltration/ HumidificationFiltersSeparators and CompactorsHumidificationServiceLTG Engineering ServicesLaboratory Test & ExperimentThermal ComfortAir Flow TestsModel Scale TestsVisualization of Air FlowsAcoustic OptimizationExperimental EvaluationReverberation Chamber MeasurementsCalorimetric Performance MeasurementsField Measurement & OptimizationMobile Filter SystemOptimization of Air Flow ProcessesEnergy Efficiency OptimizationAdjustment of Duct SystemsComfort Measurements on siteAdjustment of Induction SystemsAcoustic Measurements on siteOptimization of Filtration ProcessesSimulation & ExpertiseComputational Fluid DynamicsEnergy-efficient Flow ConceptsEvaluation of Modernisation ConceptsComparison of System SolutionsValidation of New Production ProcessesR&D & Start-upProduct Validation & DevelopmentStart-upApplication SolutionsBuilding Air ConditioningOfficeHotelSchoolHospitalLaboratoryIndustryShops & SalesMuseumAirportHomeSpecial SolutionsFood / TobaccoBakery TechnologyMeat ProcessingGrain ProcessingTobacco ProcessingPasta MachinesThermoprocessing / Process EngineeringThermoprocessingProcess EngineeringSurface technologyDrying TechnologyTextile / Nonwoven IndustryTechnical TextilesNonwoven / HygieneConstruction and insulation materialsAutomotive / Wind SimulationFahrtwind-SimulationWind TunnelMedical and Laboratory TechnologyLaboratory EquipmentMedical TextilesMedical DryersComfort Air TechnologyTransport SystemsRail TransportCommercial VehiclesMarine Travel and TransportAviationSpace TravelSolutions for other industriesPrinting and Paper TechnologyPackaging TechnologyPower Generation TechnologyAgriculture and Wood TechnologyCustomer-specific SolutionsCompanyAbout LTGWhy LTGCareers at LTGNewsEventsTerms / ConditionsDownloadsPrivacy StatementStart Privacy StatementPrivacy StatementLTG Aktiengesellschaft (abbreviated to LTG AG) welcomes you to its website. Thank you for your interest in our air-conditioning and process air technology products and services. In the following, we inform you about how and why your personal data are collected, handled and processed when you use this website. Personal dataUnless stated otherwise in the following sections, no personal data will be collected, processed or used while using this website. By preserving your anonymity some information will be transferred while accessing this website, such as your anonymised IP address. This data cannot be allocated to a certain person by us.Data protection legislation is of course complied with. Personal data within the meaning of the German Federal Data Protection Act (BDSG) includes information concerning the personal or material circumstances of an identified or identifiable individual, such as name, address, telephone number and date of birth.In the absence of explicit consent pursuant to Art. 6 para. 1 a GDPR, LTG AG processes personal data in order to fulfil a contract or if this is necessary for the implementation of pre-contractual measures pursuant to Art. 6 para. 1 b GDPR. Any further processing that takes place is necessary to safeguard a legitimate interest of our company pursuant to Art. 6 para. 1 f GDPR and outweighs the interests, fundamental rights and freedoms of the data subject. Collection of personal data when you visit our websiteWhen using the website for information purposes only, i.e. if you do not register or otherwise provide us with information, we only collect the personal data that your browser transmits to our server. If you view our website, we collect the following data, which is technically necessary for us to display our website to you and to ensure stability and security. The legal basis for this is Art. 6 para. 1 f GDPR: anonymisedIP address, date and time of the request, time zone difference to Greenwich Mean Time (GMT), content of the request (specific page), access status/HTTP status code, amount of data transmitted in each case, website from which the request comes, browser, operating system, and its interface, language and version of the browser software. ApplicationsYou can apply to our company electronically, especially by e-mail. We will of course use your data exclusively for processing your application and will not pass it on to third parties. Please note that unencrypted e-mails are not transmitted with access protection.If you have applied for a specific position and it has already been filled or if we consider you suitable for another position, we would be happy to forward your application within the company. Please let us know if you do not agree to a forwarding.Your personal data will be deleted immediately after completion of the application process or after a maximum of 6 months, unless you have expressly given us your consent for a longer storage of your data or a contract has been concluded. The legal basis is Art. 6 Para. 1 a, b and f GDPR and § 26 of the German General Data Protection Regulation (BDSG). Google AnalyticsThis website uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”; these are text files which are stored on your computer to analyse the way you use the website. The information created by the cookie about the way you use this website is usually sent to and stored on a Google server in the USA. If the IP anonymisation is activated on this website, Google will first truncate your IP address in Member States of the European Union or in other states party to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases is the full IP address sent to and truncated on a Google server in the USA. Google will use this information on behalf of the operator to evaluate the way you use the website, to collate reports on website activities and in order to provide the website operator with other services related to website and internet use. The IP address sent by your browser as part of Google Analytics is not combined with other data held by Google. You can change your browser settings to prevent cookies from being stored; however we would draw your attention to the fact that in these circumstances, you may find that you are unable to make full use of all functions on the website. You can also prevent the data (including your IP address) relating to your use of the website which is captured by the cookie being sent to or processed by Google by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available at the following Link.You can prevent data being captured by Google Analytics by clicking the following Link. An opt out cookie is then set which prevents your data being captured the next time you visit this website:For more information about the terms of use and data protection go to https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/gb.html  or https://www.google.de/intl/en/policies/. We would draw your attention to the fact that Google Analytics is supplemented by the code “gat._anonymizeIp();” on this website, to guarantee anonymised collection of IP addresses (IP masking)[gdpr_preferences text=”Cookie Preference”] Data collection and processing contact formYou can also use the form available on this website to contact us. Any data you provide us with in this connection is provided on an explicitly voluntary basis and with your consent. The legal basis for data processing in this case is Art. 6 para. 1 a GDPR. The personal data provided to us in this way will only be used for the purpose for which you have provided it. This optional information improves the handling of the contacting process and helps us to determine the specifics of your inquiry. The data will not be used for any other purposes without your express consent. You may of course revoke your consent to any future use of such data. All you need to do is contact the address stated in the legal notice section . Your data will not be passed on to third parties. NewsletterYou can subscribe to our newsletter. Your e-mail address will be needed for the registration. To be sure that you want to subscribe to the newsletter we use the so called double-opt-in process. After successful registration you receive a link via email to activate the newsletter service.   The storage of your email address serves only the purpose of being able to send you the newsletter. Of course you have the possibility to unsubscribe the newsletter and to revoke your consent for the future.The legal basis for the processing of the data after registration for the newsletter by the user is, with the user’s consent, Art. 6 para. 1 a GDPR. Data transmissionA transfer of your data to third parties does not take place, unless we are legally obliged to do so, or the transfer of data is necessary for the execution of the contractual relationship, or you have previously expressly consented to the transfer of your data.External service providers and partner companies such as online payment providers or the shipping company commissioned with the delivery will only receive your data if this is necessary to process your order. In these cases, however, the scope of the transmitted data is limited to the required minimum. As far as our service providers come into contact with your personal data, we ensure within the scope of the order processing according to Art. 28 GDPR that these comply with the regulations of the data protection laws in the same way. Please also note the respective data protection information of the providers. The respective service provider is responsible for the content of external services, whereby we check the compliance of the services with the legal requirements within the scope of reasonableness.It is important to us to process your data within the EU/EEA. However, we may use service providers who process data outside the EU/EEA. In these cases, we ensure that an appropriate level of data protection is established at the recipient prior to the transfer of your personal data. This means that EU standard contractual clauses or a decision on adequacy, such as the EU Privacy Shield, achieve a level of data protection comparable to standards within the EU. Data securityLTG AG has taken extensive technical and operational security precautions to protect your data against unauthorised access or misuse. Our security procedures are reviewed at regular intervals and modified to keep pace with technological progress. Our employees receive regular training and are committed to data secrecy. Your rightsEvery data subject has the right of access under Article 15 GDPR, the right to rectification under Article 16 GDPR, the right to erasure under Article 17 GDPR, the right to restriction of processing under Article 18 GDPR, the right to object under Article 21 GDPR and the right to data portability under Article 20 GDPR. The restrictions according to §§ 34 and 35 BDSG apply to the right of access and the right of erasure.Right to objectYou can object to the use of your data for advertising purposes at any time without incurring any costs other than the transmission costs according to the basic rates.What right do you have in the event of data processing for legitimate or public interest?Pursuant to Art. 21 para. 1 GDPR, you have the right to object at any time to the processing of personal data concerning you on the basis of Art. 6 para.1 lit. e GDPR (data processing in the public interest) or Article 6 para.1 lit. f GDPR (data processing to protect a legitimate interest), this also applies to profiling based on this provision.In the event of your objection, we will no longer process your personal data unless we can prove compelling grounds for processing that outweigh your interests, rights and freedoms, or the processing serves to assert, exercise or defend legal claims.What right do you have in the event of data processing for direct marketing?If we process your personal data for direct marketing purposes, you have the right pursuant to Art. 21 para. 2 GDPR to object at any time to the processing of personal data concerning you for the purpose of such advertising, this also applies to profiling insofar as it is associated with such direct marketing.In the event of your objection to processing for direct marketing purposes, we will no longer process your personal data for these purposes.Revocation of consentYou can revoke your consent to the processing of your personal data at any time. Please note that the revocation is only valid for the future.Right to informationYou may request information as to whether we have stored personal data about you. If you wish, we will inform you of the data concerned, the purposes for which the data is processed, to whom this data is disclosed, how long the data is stored and what further rights you are entitled to with regard to this data.Further rightsIn addition, you have the right to have your data corrected or deleted. If there is no reason for further storage, we will delete your data, otherwise we will restrict processing. You may also request that we provide all personal information that you have provided to us in a structured, current and machine-readable format either to you or to a person or company of your choice.In addition, there is a right to lodge a complaint to the responsible data protection supervisory authority (Art. 77 GDPR in conjunction with § 19 BDSG).Assertion of your rightsTo exercise your rights, you can contact the controller or the data protection officer using the contact details provided. We will process your enquiries immediately and in accordance with legal requirements and inform you of the measures we have taken. Data protection officerIf you have any questions about the processing of your personal data, please contact our data protection officer. The data protection officer will also be glad to answer any queries you may have or to accept applications or complaints.Contact data for external data protection officers:E-Mail:  Datenschutzbeauftragter(at)LTG.de Name and address of the responsible authority:LTG Aktiengesellschaft Grenzstrasse 7 70435 Stuttgart Germany Tel.: +49 0711 82 01-0 Fax: +49 0711 82 01-720 E-Mail: info@LTG.deWe use cookies to optimise our content, to ensure the functionality of the website and to analyse access to our website. For comprehensive information about our use of cookies and how you can control them, please see our Privacy Statement / Publishers Details. By continuing to use the Site, you consent to the use of cookies. cookie settings. Accept
Privacy Overview
Necessary
Google Analytics Privacy OverviewWe use cookies to optimise our content, to ensure the functionality of the website and to analyse access to our website. For comprehensive information about our use of cookies and how you can control them, please see our Privacy Policy. By continuing to use the Site, you consent to the use of cookies. NecessaryWill be stored in your browser to check the cookie settings of this website.Cookie: moove_gdpr_popup disable
Google Analytics_ga: Used to differentiate between users. _gat: Used to throttle the requirement rate. _gid: Registers a unique ID that is used to generate statistical information about how the visitor uses the site.When downloading a product PDF, an event is sent as ( ga('send','event', 'language', 'number of clicks', 'name of the file') to analyze whether a file is being downloaded or not. disable
Enable All Save ChangesYour location and interest
Country * GermanyAustriaSwitzerlandItalySpainPortugalBelgiumThe NetherlandsLuxembourgFranceUnited KingdomIrelandHungaryPolandCzech RepublicRussiaBaltic StatesScandinaviaEurope (Rest)USACanadaArgentinaCentral & South AmericaTurkeyChinaJapanKoreaPakistanCIS Countries (without Russia)Middle EastSouth AsiaSoutheast AsiaAsia (Rest)AlgeriaMoroccoTunisiaAfrica (Rest)Australia & The Pacifics
Zip Code * Please choose an Application Solution or a Product. Product - Air Diffusers Air-Water Systems Air Distribution Filtration/ Humidification Fans LTG Engineering Services OR Application Solution - Building Air Conditioning Food / Tobacco Automotive / Wind Simulation Thermoprocessing / Process Engineering Medical and Laboratory Technology Textile / Nonwoven Industry Transport Systems Solutions for other industries Customer-specific Solutions
